ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Retirees 92 - 93 (Box 15, Folder 1a)
  Includes - Retirees at Clinton/Gore Rally, 1992; Sam Byer retires, 1993; Gov. Lawton Chiles, 1993; Baltimore Craft Club, 1993; NJ Gov. Florio, 1992; Evelyn Dubrow speaks to retirees; Local 324 club, 1992; "Retiring Right" session, 1992; Local 111 retirees, 1992; Jay Mazur with retirees, 1992; MD Congressman, Tom McMillen, 1992; Mid-Hudson retiree club, 1992; Club 200, 1991; Easton Mayor Thomas Goldsmith receives flood aid, 1993; Retiree Club of Locals 234-243 picnic, 1993; Retiree Club Executive Board induction, 1993
- Shop Scenes Cutters (Box 15, Folder 1b)
  Includes men working in factory; man measuring; Asian man working cutter; racks of cut fabric
- Shop Scenes Pressers (Box 15, Folder 1c)
  Includes Herman Abrams demonstrating form with a pressing iron, Feb. 1981; group scene Efrain Dominici, Carmelo Diaz, Carmelo Gonzalez, Santos Carrasquillo, Mariano Gomez, Juan Lopez; men using irons; pressers working in front of windows steam rising; man wiping brow while pressing; individual pressers
- Solidarity, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Includes D.C. Solidarity Day rally, 1991; Solidarity Day quilt, 1991; Members of Locals 426 and 402, 1991; DCB Strikers on Solidarity Day, 1991
- In Solidarity (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Includes Camp Solidarity; Local 1199 nurses strike rally, 1995; Ignacio Hernandez speaks to General Advisory Council, 1995; Joint Conference of ACTWU, ZENSEN and ILGWU, 1994; Jobs with Justice at American Signature strike, 1994; ILGers with United Farm Workers, 1994; Catfish Workers win, 1991; Ticketmaster protest, 1994; Coca-Cola rally, 1994; Chen Jingyun accepts George Meany Human Rights Award, 1993; ILGers at Daily News rally, 1990; Farm Worker supporters protest fruit stand, 1989; Eastern Airline strike, 1989; IAMAW strike supporters, 1989; 1,000's outside Rainfair, Solidarity Day pictures, 1991
- In Solidarity (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Includes - Han Dongfang, 1992; United Mine Workers rally, 1993; Whirlpool boycott, 1991; Boris Yeltsin at sewing machine, 1991; Jay Mazur addresses rally, 1990; ILGers supporting Daily News strikers, 1991; Domsey, Eastern Airlines and Greyhound strikers on 5th Ave., 1990; Camp Solidarity; ILGers march for miners; Communications Workers of America, 1989; Pittson Coal strike, 1989
- Labor Solidarity (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Includes - Domsey, Eastern Airlines and Greyhound strikers, 1990; Dance for Solidarity advertisement, 1990
- South Africa (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Includes NY ILGers join massive anti-apartheid rally, NY, 1986; Pres. Jay Mazur, with others prior to be arrested in front of the South African Consulate, 1988; Club hears Rustin on S. Africa, 1987; Exec. VP Edgar Romney, 1993; Romney addresses solidarity rally for victims of apartheid, 1992; Romney with Moses Mayekiso at a Labor Committee Against Apartheid meeting, 1987; Rally at Yankee Stadium, (circa 1980's)
- Southeast Department (Box 15, Folder 7)
  .: Includes Workers at S.I. Cutting, Opa Locka, FL, 1995; ILGWU staffers with recipients of hurricane relief, 1982; Members of Local 415-475, 1994; Clairborne negotiating committee, 1994; US Representative Lincoln Diaz-Balart with workers of Jorca Manufacturing, 1994; VP Bonanno with Admin. Asst. Spurgeion Griggs, FL Mgr. Mike Ruano and Regional Cont. Robert Cheponis, 1993; Hurricane Andrew aid arrives, 1992; Hurricane damage, 1992; Alabama workers get backpay, 1992; Atlanta ILGers in parade, 1990; "Behold Monument", part of King Center, 1991; Downtown Atlanta, 1991; The Ebenezer Baptist Church, downtown Atlanta, 1991; Tennessee state dir. Lillian Kolwyck with ILGers, 1990; ILGers march in Dr. Martin Luther King parade, 1990; Members at El Ponce de Leon show their backpay, 1990; VP Nicolas Bonanno, 1987; Local 116 Christmas parade with banner, McComb, MS, 1988; Benny Dansavage, 1988; Martin Luther King Parade, Atlanta GA, 1988; Evelyn Dubrow, 1987; VP Nicholas Bonanno, Southeast Region director with ILG veteran, 1987; ILGers with banner at King Parade, Atlanta GA, 1987; South Carolina locals, 1987; Workers at Dandridge Textile, Dandridge, TN, 1986; Local 407 members, Morristown, TN, 1986; FL governor Bob Graham, 1986; Delegates of Southeast Region Conference, Atlanta, GA, 1988; Exec. VP Edgar Romney at Dr. King Awards Breakfast, 1988; TN ILGers at a "jobs for justice" rally, 1988; Members from Abbeville Mfg. prepare at "March of Dimes" Walk-a-thon, 1988; Atlanta delegates at Braves-Astros game, GA, 1987; VP, Nicolas Bonanno, Southeast Region Dir., Atlanta, GA, 1988; Workers at Angelica Corp., Louisville, MS, 1988; Tenn. ILGers with VP Lillian Kolwych at rally, Memphis, 1988; ILGers joining hands in a chorus of "solidarity", 1987; Exec. VP Edgar Romney with Southeast staffers, 1989; Workers end strike at THM
- Statue of Liberty (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Gov. Mario Cuomo, wife Matilda and former Pres. Sol C. Chaikin, 1986; ILGWU chorus, 1986; Ellis Island, 1986; ILGWU sponsored Italian Street fair, 1986; BA Sal DeAngelis, New Rochelle, NY, 1986; ILGers from Midwest District Council, 1986; "Los Nietos del Rey", 1986; ILGWU choral director Malcolm Dobbs, 1986
- Sweatshops (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Includes sweatshop graphic, 1995; Fania Cohn, leaders of first organizing drive, 1990; Anna Galbez,, owner of D & J Fashions, Union City, NJ, 1990; VP Sal Giardina, regional dir. and Robert J. Venezia of the NJ Labor Dept., 1987; Organizing director Mike Estigo, 1987; Various sweatshop pictures, 1990 & 1991
- Trade (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Includes Saying "no" to NAFTA, 1993; "Women Workers Needed" banner, Tijuana, MX, 1993; NAFTA rally, NYC, 1993; Nick Roussos, Fall River, 1993; Anti-NAFTA rally, West Helena, Ark, 1993; Anti-NAFTA rally, Harrisburg, PA, 1993; Anti-NAFTA rally in El Peso, TX, 1993; Anti-NAFTA parade, Chicago, III, 1993; Signing petitions, Illinois State Fair, 1993; Anti-NAFTA banner, MD, 1993; Anti-NAFTA signs, San Francisco, CA, 1993; Allentown Mgr. Sam Cavalieri and Easton Mgr. Earl Laub with Rep. McHale, 1993; Anti-NAFTA banner at Ohio rally, 1993; PBS advertisement for documentary, 1993; Otto Kuczynski, president of Fairfield Textiles at NJ NAFTA hearing, 1993; Glens Falls, NY demonstration, 1986; ILGers rally in MA, 1986; ILGers rally in Miami, FL, 1986; ILGers leaflet downtown Cleveland, 1986; Rayda Rivera speaks on Capitol Hill, 1986; Nicholas Bonanno, director of the Southern Region with Rep. Kenneth H. "Buddy" McKay (D-FL), 1987; Cartoon for "unfair imports"; VP Sal Giardina and International Relations Dir. Michele Briones with Japanese unionists, North Bergen, NJ, 1987; Unemployed NJ workers interviewed, 1986; VP Giardina, Local 134 pres. Florence DiStefano, Local 158 pres. Angelo Spalluto and NJ Congresswoman Marge Roukena, 1987; Congressmen Chalmers Wylie and John Kasich with Ohio ILGers, 1987; House Majority Whip Tony Coelho and Evelyn Dubrow, 1987; ILGers handing out leaflets in Cleveland, OH, 1987; Leafleting in Miami, Fl, 1987; Cartoon for "Far East Imports", 1981; Leafleting and demonstration against "Character" closing union shops, 1975
- Trade (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Includes - Pres. Jay Mazur at FFACT conference, Washington, D.C., 1988; Exec. VP Edgar Romney addresses NYC NAFTA rally, 1993; AFL-CIO pres. Lane Kirkland and Sec'y-Treas. Thomas Donohue, 1993; Demonstrators protest Pres. Bush signing Mexico trade deal, Los Angeles, CA, 1993; Bergan-Hudson ILGers demonstrate against NAFTA, Union City, NJ, 1993; Pres. Jay Mazur and ACTWU pres. Jack Sheinkman at NY City Hall, 1993; ILGers on Nightline talk about "importing jobs", 1992; Cartoon for "Runaway Factories by Carol Simpson, 1992; Advertisement for "Sonneti Classic Jeans", 1990; ILGers at import rally, Capitol Hill, 1990; Carmen Sosa's neighborhood in the Dominican Republic, 1993; AFL-CIO Sec'y-Treas. Tom Donohue, 1988; Representative Pat Williams, 1988; VP Ron Alman, dir. of the New England Region, John Crowley, asst. education dir. with Rep. Joseph Kennedy Jr. (D-Mass), 1987; Anti-NAFTA rally in front of General Motors building, NYC, 1993; LA members protest outside pro-NAFTA conference, 1993; ILGers from Harrisburg, PA, 1990
- Triangle Fire (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Includes Young People pay tribute to Triangle Fire victims, 1994; VP Evelyn Dubrow during "Triangle" ceremony, 1989; Local 155 during "wreath-laying" ceremony honoring "Triangle" victims, 1995; Firefighters battling the "Triangle" fire, 1991; Fire Commissioner Howard Safir, 1994; NYC Mayor David Dinkins speaks at "Triangle" ceremony, 1993; Members of Ladder Co. 20 (which responded to the 1911 fire) symbolically raises their ladders to the sixth floor, 1990; Triangle rally pictures, 1990; Michael Grimaldi, manager of the Nassau-Suffolk Dis., with Pauline Pepe the last survivor of the triangle fire, 1992; Members of Ladder Co. 20 honored, 1990; Pres. Jay Mazur and Mayor David Dinkins observe a moment of silence for triangle tragedy, 1991; Pres. Jay Mazur addressing the crowd, 1988; Teacher talks to her fourth grade class about the tragedy, 1988; VP Sal Giardina, Pres. Mazur, Justice Editor Emeritus Leon Stein, and Bunny Kuiken, Botto interim dir. at Triangle Fire exhibit at Botto House, Haledon, NJ, 1987; Fire Commissioner Joseph E. Spinnato at exhibit, 1987; AFL-CIO Secretary-Treasurer Thomas Donohue and Evelyn Dubrow at exhibit, 1987; Leon Stein addressing Triangle crowd, 1987; Poet Chris Llewellyn reads from her book Fragments from the Fire, 1987; Leon Stein visits triangle exhibit, 1986
- Union Label Promotions (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Includes Woman marking weekly planner; Children in beach setting surrounded by Union Label; Children in rain with Union Label bags; Woman turning off Union Label alarm clock; Educational poster
- Union Label Products (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Includes 1995 Union Label calendar mock-ups; Union Label product pictures: T-shirts, jackets, alarm clock, duffel bag, sweatshirt, umbrella, wristwatch, beach towel, pen; Union Label fabric, 1990; Clothing and product models; Union Label contact sheets
- Union Label TV commercial (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Includes Head shots of various actors; Chorus rehearsing on stage; Chorus backstage; In the dressing room; Filming of chorus; Filming of actors; In the control room; Shot of television playing commercial
- Union Labels (Box 16, Folder 9)
  labels being sewn into clothing
- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Includes hospital operating room and medical staff
- Personalities A (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Includes Gary Alder; Local 23-25 with "register to vote" banner; Ronald Alman, 1982; Jay Mazur, Tony {Scilito}; Luigi Antonini; Shelley Appleton; Milton Arons, 1961; Morres Ashfes
- Personalities B (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Includes Sam Bergman; Joseph Barondess; Abraham Baroff; Louise Jones and Nester Berger; Marty Berger; Nick Bonanno; Pres. George Bush Sr. Heyward Brown; Boxer Riddick Bowe with his mother; Betty Boyer, Central States asst. org. dir., Dallas; Ted Bernstein; Irving Bakal; Morris Bagno; Angelica Balabanoff; Angela [Bamdroci}; Alben Barkley; Murray Baron; Abe Beacon; Harry Berger; Morris Biolis; Grace Birkel; Max Bluestein; LA Mayor Tom Bradley; Justice Louis D. Brandeis; Ray Bramucci; Louis Brass; Andrew {Bieniller}; Joseph Breslaw; Si Bresner; Israel Breslow; Irving Brown; CA Governor Brown; Jerry Brown; Ralph {Beuche}; Sam Byer; Robert Byrd; Louis Rolnick with ILGWU health director Theodore Bernstein, 1980; Millie Ballon; Bill Bradley; Former Georgia Governor Carl Sanders, Nickolas Bonanno and Sen. Ernest Hollings; Leon Blum
- Personalities C (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Includes Veep Glen Clay, Education Dir, Central States Region with ILG Political Committee and Congressman William Clay of MS; Cesar Chavez with VP Cornelius Wall; Former Pres. Jimmy Carter and Sol Chaikin, 1976; Frannie Cohn; Frank {Crosswaith}; Hillary Clinton; Hillary with Pres. Jay Mazur; Pres. Bill Clinton and Al Gore, 1992; Ceasar Chavez drawing; Doris Ling Cohan; Cesar Chavez; Mario Cuomo; Teamsters pres. Ron Carey; Mgr. Sam Cavalieri; Pres. Sol Chaikin on MacNeil-Lehrer Report; Jewish Daily Forward editor Abraham Cahan; Chaikin with sculptor Chaim Gross, 1983; Hugh Carey, 1974; Rosalyn Carter with Wilbur Daniels; Yvette Charpentier; Abe Cahan with David Dubinsky, 1940; Eli Charne; Ceasar Chavez and Cornelius Walls; Glen Clay; Joseph Clayman; Fannia Cohn; Max Cohn; Marty Cohen; Lewis Corey; Alan {Cramton}; M.J. Coldwell, parliamentary leader of the Cooperative Commonwealth Federation of Canada with Mark Starr, ILGWU educational dir. and VP Isidore Nagler; George Counts; Carter and Chaikin at 1980 Democratic Convention
- Chaikin, Sol (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Includes ILGWU Seminar, Mont Gabriel, 1973; Chaikin and Pres. Jay Mazur, 1983 Convention; Chaikin and former NY governor Mario Cuomo, 1982; Chaikin with cast and director (Michael Libassi) of "Looking for the Union Label", Chaikin being interview on NY television station WPIX by former deputy mayor Herman Badillo, 1980; Chaikin on front cover of "The New York Times", 1976; Chaikin awarded an honorary Doctor of Humane Letters degree, 1980; Chaikin receives honorary degree from Rutgers University, 1980; Chaikin with wife, AFL-CIO pres. Lane Kirkland and Jack Hockman, Local 66 manager and chairman of the home's board of directors, 1980; Chaikin with Louis Silver, exec. dir. of the Workmen's Circle Home, 1980; Chaikin lights the largest Chanukah menorah, NYC, 1980; Chaikin with Jimmy Carter and Murray Finley, President of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), 1979; Chaikin at White House Labor Day picnic, 1979; Chaikin testifying before the National Commission on Unemployment Insurance in NYC, 1979; Chaikin with US Secretary of Labor Ray Marshall, 1978; Chaikin with Irving Brown, AFL-CIO European representative and Henoch Mendelsund, dir. of ILGWU International Affairs Dept., 1978; Chaikin at ACTWU convention, Los Angeles, CA, 1978; Chaikin with Herbert W. Baker, US labor attach to Italy, Mendelsund and Daniel Goott, State Dept. adviser on European labor affairs, 1978; Chaikin at City College of NY luncheon, 1978; Chaikin at GEB meeting, Florida, 1978; Chaikin at luncheon, Boston, MA, 1978; Chaikin with retirees at annual concert, Miami Beach Theater, FL; Chaikin with Michael Dukakis and New England dir. Edward Milano, MA, 1978; Chaikin accepting Histadrut Humanitarian Award, 1978; Chaikin addressing meeting of New York Coat, Suit, Dress, 1978; Chaikin with Tom Brokaw on NBC-TV's "Today Show", 1978
- Chaikin, Sol (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Includes - Chaikin at labor seminar sponsored by League for Industrial Democracies, 1977; Chaikin with Howard Coughlin of OEIU and arbitration assoc. Pres. Robert Colson, 1977; Chaikin with Walter Mondale, 1977; Chaikin with AFL-CIO pres. George Meany, 1976; Chaikin with IUD Sec'y-Treas. Jacob Clayman at the Industrial Union Dept. convention, 1977; Chaikin in Allentown, PA, 1974; Chaikin with House Majority Leader Tip O'Neill, Evelyn Dubrow and Congressman Edward P. Boland, 1976; Chaikin with Dubrow and Majority Whip John J. McFall, 1976; Chaikin at economic summit, Tokyo, 1979; Chaikin with Brokaw on Today Show, 1980; Chaikin with Walter Mondale at Garment Center Rally, 1984; Chaikin with Jimmy Carter; Chaikin with Rhode Island Laborites at Rhode Island State AFL-CIO convention, 1974; Chaikin with secretary Miriam Sluckan during GEB meeting, 1982; Chaikin and David Dubinsky; Chaikin with Sec'y-Treas. Shelley Appleton and Yook Chee Hom, chairperson of the Sportswear Joint Board, 1980; Chaikin with district council mgr. Donald Kret, 1980; Chaikin with NAACP Exec. Dir. Benjamin Hooks, 1978; Chaikin, wife, Rosalind and Yugoslavian dissident writer Mihajlo Mihajlov, 1979; Chaikin and Mondale, 1979; Chaikin and Tip O'Neill, 1978; Chaikin at Democratic National Convention, 1980; Chaikin honored at Social Democrats USA annual dinner, 1979; Chaikin interviewed at Wilkes-Barre meeting, 1979
- Chaikin and Others (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Chaikin With Pres. Jimmy Carter; Chaikin with Louis Strassberg and Wilbur Daniels, 1974; Chaikin with Jacob Sheinkman, Edward Schneider, Albert Shanker, and Lane Kirkland, 1975; Delivering speech, 1975; Chaikin with VT Gov. Thomas Salmon, 1976; Chaikin with Abba Eban, Louis Stulberg and David Dubinsky, 1975; Chaikin at Jewish Labor Committee dinner, 1977; Chaikin at meeting of Columbia University Labor Seminar, 1977; Chaikin prepares for TV ad, 1976; Chaikin with Dr. Lev E. Dubinsky, 1976; Chaikin on bicentennial march, 1976; Chaikin at immigration conference, 1976; Chaikin and Sol Stetin, 1976; With Patrick Moynihan, Harry Van Arsdale, Greg Bardacke, and Albert Shanker, 1975; With Jay Mazur, Arthur Silverstein, Christine Scott, and Shelley Appleton, 1975
- Chaikin and Others (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Includes - Chaikin with wife Roslyn, and Harry Van Arsdale, 1975; Chaikin and Jacob Sheinkman receiving League for Industrial Democracy awards, 1975; Chaikin speaking at dinner for Murray H. Finley, 1975; Chaikin and I. W. Abel, 1975; Chaikin and Julian F. Carper, 1974; Chaikin with Jacob Sheinkman, Jacob S. Potofsky, Yehoshua Levy and Murray H. Finley, 1973; Chaikin at JLC dinner, 1975; Chaikin with Ed Koch, 1976; Chaikin and Albert Shanker; Chaikin and General Grigorenko, 1978; Chaikin and Leon Stein; Chaikin and Walter Mondale, 1977; Chaikin and Abe Beame
- Stulberg, Dubinsky and Chaikin (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Includes picture of Chaikin, Dubinsky and Stulberg together
- Dubinsky, David - Portraits (missing from box 6/2/2017) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Includes various portraits and individual photos
- Dubinsky, David (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Includes Dubinsky voting in Local 10 elections, 1953; Dubinsky receiving honorary degree from Brandeis University, 1966; Dubinsky with Francis Perkins and Rose Schneiderman at Triangle Fire plaque dedication, 1961; Dubinsky speaking before Senate labor subcommittee, 1955; Dubinsky showing his cutter skills, 1957; Dubinsky speaking at 25th anniversary of his presidency ball, 1957; Dubinsky at ILG sponsored serviceman's club; Dubinsky at ILG sponsored FDR Institute in Mondello, Italy; Dubinsky walking the picket line; Dubinsky riding bicycles with grand-daughter Ryna; Dubinsky with war orphans at 1950 convention, 1950; Dubinsky with Presidential Medal of Freedom, awarded to him by LBJ, 1969; Dubinsky delivering speeches; Dubinsky's wife, Emma, daughter Jean Appleton and granddaughter Ryna; 1959 convention delegates demonstrate for Dubinsky's re-election, 1959; Eulogizing Dubinsky at memorial service: AFL-CIO Pres. Lane Kirkland, Sol. Chaikin, Shelley Appleton, biographer Abe Raskin, Joe Glazer and Bayard Rustin, 1982; Dedication of Dubinsky Student Center, 1975
- Dubinsky, David (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Includes Dubinsky greeting President Eisenhower; Dubinsky with then Senator John F Kennedy, 1956; Lyndon Johnson helping Dubinsky with his coat; Dubinsky and Robert Kennedy; Dubinsky and Eleanor Roosevelt at NRA Coat and Suit Label Inauguration, 1933; Francis Perkins and Dubinsky, mid 1930's; Dubinsky, Phillip Murray, Hannah Haskel and Sidney Hillman on Boardwalk in Atlantic City, NJ; Dubinsky with former French Premier Leon Blum; Dubinsky with John F Kennedy, Alex Rose and Prof. John Childs, 1960; Dubinsky dining with John D Rockefeller, Jr.; Dubinsky at the White House with Franklin Delano Roosevelt for showing of "Pins and Needles", 1938; Dubinsky with William Green celebrating affiliation with AFL in 1940; Dubinsky with Former NY Gov. Herbert Lehman and NYC mayor Robert F. Wagner at end of 1958 dress strike; Dubinsky and John L. Lewis; Lyndon Johnson with Dubinsky for speech; Dubinsky shaking hand with NRA officials; Dubinsky with Eleanor Roosevelt and Adlai Stevenson during 1956 Presidential campaign
- David Dubinsky (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Includes Dubinsky, Julius Hochman and Pres. Benjamin Schlesinger in Atlantic city, ca 1920's; Dubinsky with Eleanor Roosevelt and Red Cross officials; Dubinsky photographing wife Emma, George and Eugenia Meany; Dubinsky receiving award from Italian Pres. Giuseppe Saragat, 1966; In Israel, Dubinsky with first Premier David Ben Gurion; Dubinsky and Chief Justice Earl Warren; Dubinsky and Presidential advisor Bernard Baruch; Dubinsky, Grover Whalen, Julius Hochman, A. I. Agree, Albert Florsheimer, Jacob Siegel, Alfred Lasher, Chas Robbins and Harry Rubenstein signing agreement in NY Dress Industry, 8/19/1933; Presenting Humanitarian award to VP Hubert H Humphrey on behalf of Histadrut, 1967; Dubinsky with John Dewey on Dewey's 90th birthday, 1949; Dubinsky with Hannah Haskel and Louis Stuhlberg after convention, 1962; Dubinsky with Luis Munoz Marin and Hugh Gaitskell; Dubinsky with Norman Thomas and Walker Reuther; Dubinsky and Herbert Morrison, 1962; Chaikin, Dubinsky, Stulberg and Abba Eban at luncheon, 1975; Dubinsky and Hannah Haskel
- 25th Anniversary of Dubinskys Presidency (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Includes Buses leaving from Philadelphia for Madison Square Garden; Speeches given at MSG; Dubinsky posing with gifts; Celebration at Unity House; Dubinsky's family, wife Emma, daughter Jean Appleton, and granddaughter Ryna
- Dubrow, Evelyn (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Includes - Congressman Richard Bolling and Evelyn Dubrow; Evelyn Dubrow speaking with members; Evelyn Dubrow on the steps of Capitol Hill with Jay Mazur and others, 1987; Evelyn Dubrow with Senator Paul Douglas; Evelyn Dubrow, Abe Ribicoff, and Sen. Douglas; Evelyn Dubrow at White house with Pres. Johnson and Lady Bird Johnson; Evelyn Dubrow testifying; Evelyn Dubrow and Doug Levin; Evelyn Dubrow and Esther Peterson, 1977; Evelyn Dubrow testifying with Sol Chaikin, 1980; Dubrow supporting Mondale at '84 convention; Evelyn Dubrow presenting petition, 1988; Dubrow receiving Child Care Challenge Pioneer award presented by Congresswomen Pat Schroeder and Olympia Snowe, 1988; At '88 Democratic convention, Dubrow, VP Kolwyck, Ed Vargas and Pres. Jay Mazur; Singing in solidarity Dubrow and Mazur, 1986; Dubrow and Wilbur Daniels testify
- Personalities D (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Includes - Malcom Dodds; Portrait of Mary E. Dreier; Prof. John T. Dunlop with AFL-CIO officials, Lane Kirkland and Thomas R. Donahue, 1994; Portrait of David Dinkins; John Dyche; Portraits and individual photos of Wilbur Daniels; Wilbur Daniels and Sol Chaikin; Max Danish; Max Danish speaking to Francis Perkins and David Dubinsky; Harry Crone and Max Danish, 1938; Portrait of Eugene Debs; Pete Detlefsen, 1976; Cliff Depin, 1977; Louis Dworkin; Joseph L. Dubrow; Senator Thomas Dodd; Abe Dolgen; Melvyn Douglas, 1960; Senator Paul Douglas; Benny Dansavage; General Dwight Eisenhower with John Dewey, 1949
- Personalities E (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Includes Aaron Einbinder, Philadelphia joint board installation meeting; Sam Eisenberg, Local 132; President Dwight D Eisenhower; Pres. Eisenhower and William Green; Pres. Eisenhower, William Green, and George Meany; Arthur A. Elder; Henryk Erlich
- Personalities F (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Includes Barney Frank and Sol Chaikin, 1983; Jay Mazur with Ralph and Eva Fasanella present deed to Ann Belkov; 1991 Ralph Fasanella, 1991; James Farmer receiving award from OPEN society, Hugh Schwartzberg, Jay Mazur, David Dinkins and Morris Milgram, 1991; Mabel Fuller receiving Red Cross citation from two servicemen; Mabel Fuller and Eleanor Roosevelt; Arthur Flemming testifying; President Gerald Ford; Z. Freedman; Morris P. Feinstein; Murray Finley; Harry Fisher; Mary Flowers being sworn in by Edward Kramer, 1981; Moe Falikman; Simon Farber; Israel Feinberg; Sam Fine; Mayer Finkel, 1969; Carmen (Ortiz) Finnegan; Harry Fisher; Ralph Fasanella in shop, negative only
- Samuel Gompers (Box 19, Folder 3)